//問題文を格納する要素です
const quiz = [
    {
      question: "Visitors to the mural exhibition at the Vancouver National Museum are encouraged to make a small _____.",
      answers: ["appreciation", "reputation", "inauguration", "donation"],
      correct: "donation"
    },
    {
      question: "The general _____ among the directors was that the company should immediately recall the defective device.",
      answers: ["productivity", "consensus", "patent", "compensation"],
      correct: "consensus"
    },
    {
      question: "In the last quarter, there was a sharp _____ in the number of mergers and acquisitions in the technology sector.",
      answers: ["increase", "addition" ,"round", "property"],
      correct: "increase"
    },
    {
      question: "Meernox has been expanding its operations into other states and will have a _____ of thirty retail outlets nationwide by the end of December.",
      answers: ["total", "number", "quantity", "limit"],
      correct: "total"
    },
    {
      question: "Since BCL, Inc., does not have enough money in the budget, it cannot upgrade its _____ on time.",
      answers: ["liaisons", "figures", "facilities", "warranties"],
      correct: "facilities"
    },
    {
      question: "_____ to the content hall will be restricted to authorized personnel until tomorrow morning.",
      answers: ["Admission", "Advance", "Remedy", "Solution"],
      correct: "Admission"
    },
    {
      question: "As the job _____ stipulates, all candidates need to have a bechelor's degree in economics.",
      answers: ["shipment", "description", "performance", "relocation"],
      correct: "description"
    },
    {
      question: "A _____ of knowledge about Spring Data Systems is needed for all applications desiring to work for SDS Co.Ltd.",
      answers: ["wealth", "width", "convenience", "delay"],
      correct: "wealth"
    },
    {
      question: "The sales assistants at Sula's Department Store always greet customers in a courteous _____.",
      answers: ["prescription", "remark", "manner", "progress"],
      correct: "manner"
    },
    {
      question: "An assessment of overseas academic _____ is necessary before applying for the one-year internship in London.",
      answers: ["apologies", "resignations", "qualifications", "ceremonies"],
      correct: "qualifications"
    },
    {
      question: "One of the primary goals of LCC, Inc., is to accommodate a wide _____ of customer needs.",
      answers: ["patron", "range", "contract", "rate"],
      correct: "range"
    },
    {
      question: "After a week-long _____, the entrepreneur Kevin Miyata announced his intention to establish a new chain of restaurants in Switzerland.",
      answers: ["deliberation", "portion", "certainty", "privilege"],
      correct: "deliberation"
    }
  ];
